{
    "subject": "resource/Key_Largo_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_crime_thriller_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Key Largo (film) is American crime thriller films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8205415606498718,
            "question": "What makes Key Largo a representative example of the American crime thriller genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8050510883331299,
            "question": "Can you compare and contrast Key Largo with other American crime thriller films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.676477313041687,
            "question": "What genre is the film Key Largo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6228710412979126,
            "question": "What elements typically define an American crime thriller film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5986753106117249,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in American crime thriller films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5765514969825745,
            "question": "What country are American crime thriller films typically from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5712416172027588,
            "question": "Can you name other examples of American crime thriller films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5517274737358093,
            "question": "Are there any subgenres within American crime thriller films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.503838300704956,
            "question": "Is Key Largo a romance film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33447185158729553,
            "question": "How has the American crime thriller genre evolved over time?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Key Largo (film) is American crime thriller films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3226_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Key Largo a romance film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3226_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any subgenres within American crime thriller films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3226_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name other examples of American crime thriller films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3226_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3226_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3226_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3226_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3226_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3226_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3226_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3226_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3226_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3226_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3226_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide various details about the film \"Key Largo,\" including its classification as a \"stylish dramatic thriller\" and a \"crime-gangster melodrama.\" These descriptions align with it being categorized under American crime thriller films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}